# JOSHUA PRUITT

Full Stack Developer

# **PROFILE**

Currently 20 years of age, born in 2004. Born in St. George, Utah.

Expertise in computer programming and software engineering. Interested in all thing's computers. Looking to go back to college to finish my education. Planning to get a degree in game design.

Planning on getting my master's degree and getting a PHD in a computer programing and design related field.

### CONTACT

PHONE: 702-708-7637

WEBSITE:

https://ioshuapruitt.netlifv.app/

**EMAIL:** 

joshuapruitt6484@gmail.com

## **HOBBIES**

- Building Model Kits
- Playing and creating Video Games
- Building Computers
- Watching movies

#### **EDUCATION**

#### Full Stack Developer Bootcamp

June 2024 - Current

Coded full stack applications using a variety of tools like, JavaScript, Node.js, MongoDB, Postgres, and React.

#### College of Southern Nevada

2024 - June 2024

4.0 GPA during spring semester. Was on the dean's list at the end of the semester.

#### **Shadow Ridge High**

2021 - 2022 High school diploma.

#### **WORK EXPERIENCE**

#### Joann - General team Member

August 2023 – January 2024

Used Joann's system to help customers purchase items. Answering phones and solving customer dilemmas. Keeping shelves stocked and clean. Recovering misplaced stock and placing them in the correct places. Keeping the workplace tidy and clean and closing the store.

#### Pizza Hut - Cook

September 2021 – April 2022

General duties include, preparing and cooking food, keeping the work area tidy and clean, prepping items to be ready to use.

#### **SKILLS**

- JavaScript, HTML, and CSS
- TypeScript and Node.js Development
- React JavaScript and React TypeScript
- Postgres, PostgreSQL, and Sequelize Development
- MongoDB and Mongoose Development